[
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "How are notes the go off the stave drawn?",
    "incorrect": [
      "With letters",
      "With added squares",
      "With added circles"
    ],
    "correct": "With added lines"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note above the stave with no added lines?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "B",
      "A"
    ],
    "correct": "G"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note above the stave with one added line through it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "B",
      "G"
    ],
    "correct": "A"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note above the stave with one added line underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "D",
      "G"
    ],
    "correct": "B"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note above the stave with one line through it and one underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A",
      "B",
      "G"
    ],
    "correct": "C"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note above the stave with two lines underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "B",
      "G"
    ],
    "correct": "D"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note below the stave with no added lines?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A",
      "B",
      "C"
    ],
    "correct": "D"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note below the stave with one added line through it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "G",
      "B",
      "D"
    ],
    "correct": "C"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note below the stave with one added line above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "G",
      "C",
      "A"
    ],
    "correct": "B"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note below the stave with one line through it and one line above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "G",
      "C",
      "B"
    ],
    "correct": "A"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In treble clef, what is the note below the stave with two lines above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "D",
      "C",
      "B"
    ],
    "correct": "G"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note above the stave with no added lines?",
    "incorrect": [
      "E",
      "D",
      "C"
    ],
    "correct": "B"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note above the stave with one added line through it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "F",
      "E",
      "D"
    ],
    "correct": "C"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note above the stave with one added line underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "B",
      "E",
      "F"
    ],
    "correct": "D"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note above the stave with one line through it and one underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "B",
      "F"
    ],
    "correct": "E"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note above the stave with two lines underneath it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "B",
      "E"
    ],
    "correct": "F"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note below the stave with no added lines?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "D",
      "E"
    ],
    "correct": "F"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note below the stave with one added line through it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "C",
      "D",
      "F"
    ],
    "correct": "E"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note below the stave with one added line above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "F",
      "C",
      "B"
    ],
    "correct": "D"
  },

  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note below the stave with one line through it and one line above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "F",
      "D",
      "B"
    ],
    "correct": "C"
  },
  
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "stave",
    "question": "In bass clef, what is the note below the stave with two lines above it?",
    "incorrect": [
      "D",
      "C",
      "F"
    ],
    "correct": "B"
  }
]
